A Guide to the Governor J. Lindsay Almond, Jr., Executive records, 1958-1962
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Judicial, 1958-1962., Extent: 3 cu. ft. [6 boxes]. (Box 179-184)
  - Attorney General, 1960 (Box 179)
  - Attorney General, 1961-1962 (Box 179)
  - Attorney General, Motion Picture Censorship (Box 180)
  - Attorney General, War Veterans Claims, 1958-1961 (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, First Judicial Circuit and Recommendations (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, Fourth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, Sixteenth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, Twenty-fourth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, Twenty-eighth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, Twenty-eighth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations, Reed-Underwood, 1959 (Box 180)
  - Circuit Courts, Twenty-eighth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations, Wahab, Whitley, Wood house, 1958 (Box 181)
  - Circuit Courts, Twenty-eighth Judicial Circuit and Recommendations, Misc. (Box 181)
  - Circuit Courts, Thirty-third Judicial Circuit (Box 181)
  - Circuit Courts, Misc., 1958-1962 (Box 181)
  - City Courts, Other than Corporation, Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court (Box 181)
  - City Courts, Other than Corporation, Law and Chancery Court, Misc. (Box 181)
  - City Courts, Other than Corporation, Law and Equity, Richmond, Judges, Recommendations (Box 181)
  - City Courts, Other than Corporation, Police Courts and Commonwealth Attorney (Box 182)
  - Corporation Courts, Judges, Misc. (Box 182)
  - Corporation Courts, Lynchburg, City of (Box 182)
  - Corporation Courts, Newport News, City of (Box 182)
  - Corporation Courts, Norfolk, City of (Box 182)
  - Hustings Court, Undated (Box 182)
  - Hustings Courts, City of Portsmouth (Box 182)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, 1958-1960 (Box 182)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Recommendations, 1958 (Box 183)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Recommendations, 1960 (Box 183)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Virginia, 1961-1962 (Box 184)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Retirement, 1957-1961 (Box 184)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Retirement Mr. Justice Willis D. Miller (Box 184)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Retirements and Resignations, 1958-1961 (Box 184)
  - General, Court CLerks Association (Box 184)
  - General, Estate of Granville P. Meade, 1958-1961 (Box 184)
  - General, Justices of the Peace (Box 184)
  - General, United States District Court, 1958-1961
  - General, United States Supreme Court (Box 184)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous, 1958-1962., Extent: 1.5 cu. ft. [3 boxes]. (Box 185-187)
  The Miscellaneous records are housed in 3 boxes and contain personal correspondence with political figures and printed reports of state agencies. Personal correspondence to Governor Almond include: Watkins A. Abbitt, John S. Battle, Harry F. Byrd, Harry F. Byrd, Jr., A. Willis Robertson, Thomas B. Stanley and William M. Tuck.
  - Political figures, Abbitt, Watkins, Mr. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Almond, J. Lindsay (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Battle, John S. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Byrd, Harry F. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Byrd, Harry F., Jr. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Downing, Thomas N., Jr. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Gary, J. Vaughan (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Hardy, Porter, Jr. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Harrison, Burr P. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Jennings, Pat W. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Lowance, Carter O., 1958 January-June (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Lowance, Carter O., 1958 July-December (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Poff, Richard H. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Robeson, Edward J., Jr. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Robeson, Edward J., Jr. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Robertson, A. Willis (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Smith, Howard W. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Stanley, Thomas B. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Stephens, A.E.S. (Box 185)
  - Political figures, Tuck, William M. (Box 185)
  - Printed matter and reports of State Organizations (Box 186)
  - Reports of State Agencies (Box 187)